

MIKITA

KANSTANTSINAU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER

CONTACTS

Address: Sulaberidze st., Batumi, Georgia

Email: nick.konstantinov.job@

gmail.com

Telegram: @nick_konstantinov LinkedIn: Mikita Kanstantsinau GitHub: nick-konstantinov

HARD SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

JS JavaScript

TS TypeScript

Angular (basic knowledge)

Webpack

SOFT SKILLS

BEM/OOP/SOLID/FIRST

🕰 Agile (Scrum, Kanban)

REST/HTTP/HTTPS

Version control (Git)

Ps Graphics editors (Ps, Figma)

LANGUAGES

English:

A2 (Pre-Intermediate)

Russian:

Native

AWARDS





Hello, I 'm a software development engineer. I 'm interested in animating static artists` or designers` templates to life. And I also enjoy creating convenient and interactive interfaces for websites and applications.

Many years of experience as a teacher allowed me to develop communication skills and the ability to express my thoughts and ideas clearly, and my experience as an engineer allowed me to find effective solutions to complex problems. As a chief engineer, I successfully managed a team of specialists, distributing tasks and responsibilities. I consider my strengths are the ability to work in a team, involvement in the process of working on a project and the ability to put myself in the shoes of the customer or the end user in order to improve the product I create.

At the moment my goal is to become a successful frontend developer who can handle complex tasks on different projects. To do this, I continue studying hard and every day I learn something new and hone my knowledge in practice.

EDUCATION

HIGHER EDUCATION

◆ 2008 — 2013

«Organization and Management of Foundry Production» / «Machinery and Foundry Technology» / Bachelor`s degree

Gomel State Technical University named after P.O. Sukhoi

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

♦ December, 2022 — August, 2023

Online training course «UpSkill Me» / JS / Front-End «RS School»

November, 2022

Online training course «IT Fundamentals» / «Basics of Computer Science. Basics of Programming. Math for IT»

«EPAM Learn Platform»

March, 2022 — April, 2022

Online training course «HTML5» / «CSS3»

«SoloLearn»

July, 2021 — January, 2022

Training course «Basic knowledge of programming and algorithm knowledge using C language and JS»

«IT Class» / Gomel

♦ 2006 — 2008

Training for the profession of «Computer Operator»

Educational Institution «Inter-School UPKNº1» / Gomel

WORK EXPIRIENCE

2018 — 2022

Chief Engineer

LLC «Prompodgotovka» / Gomel

Teacher

Private Educational Institution «Center for training, advanced training and retraining of workers «Prompodgotovka–Obrazovanie» / Gomel

♦ 2013 — 2015

Process engineer

OJSC «Gomel Foundry «CENTROLIT» / Gomel

REFERENCES

Andrian Chernenkov

LLC «Prompodgotovka» / Director

Stanislav Shevtsov

PEI «Prompodgotovka-Obrazovanie» / Director

Email: prompodgotovka@mail.ru

Email: dkranprom@mail.ru



НИКИТА КОНСТАНТИНОВ

ИНЖЕНЕР-РАЗРАБОТЧИК ПРОГРАММНОГО ОБЕСПЕЧЕНИЯ

КОНТАКТЫ

ул. Сулаберидзе, Адрес Батуми, Грузия

nick.konstantinov.job@

amail.com

Telegram: @nick_konstantinov LinkedIn: Mikita Kanstantsinau GitHub: nick-konstantinov

проф. НАВЫКИ



Fmail:

CSS3

JavaScript

TypeScript

Angular (базовые знания)

Webpack

ДОП. НАВЫКИ

BEM / OOP / SOLID / FIRST

Agile (Scrum, Kanban)

REST / HTTP / HTTPS

Система контроля версий (Git)

Ps Граф. редакторы (Ps, Figma)

языки

Английский:

А2 (Пред. средний уровень)

Ф Русский:

Родной

НАГРАДЫ





профиль

Привет, я инженер-разработчик программного обеспечения. Мне интересно оживлять статичные шаблоны художников или дизайнеров. А также создавать удобные и интерактивные интерфейсы сайтов и приложений.

Многолетний опыт работы преподавателем позволил мне развить навыки коммуникации и умение четко доносить свои мысли и идеи, а опыт работы инженером - находить эффективные решения сложных задач. Будучи главным инженером я успешно руководил командой специалистов, распределяя задания и обязанности. Мои сильные стороны: умение работать в команде, вовлеченность в процесс работы над проектом и способность поставить себя на место заказчика или конечного пользователя чтобы улучшить продукт, который я создаю.

На данный момент моя цель — стать успешным фронтенд-разработчиком, способным решать сложные задачи в разных проектах. Для этого я продолжаю усердно учиться и каждый день изучаю что-то новое и оттачиваю знания на практике.

ОБРАЗОВАНИЕ

ВЫСШЕЕ ОБРАЗОВАНИЕ

2008 — 2013

«Организация и управление литейным производством» / «Машины и технология литейного производства» / Инженер

Гомельский государственный технический университет имени П.О.Сухого

ΔΟΠΟΛΗΜΤΕΛЬΗΟΕ Ο ΕΡΑЗΟΒΑΗΜΕ

Декабрь, 2022 — Август, 2023

Онлайн-курс «UpSkill Me» / JS / Front-End

«PS School» Ноябрь 2022

Онлайн курс «IT Fundamentals» «Основы информатики / Основы программирования / Математика для ИТ»

«EPAM Learn Platform»

Март, 2022 — Апрель, 2022

Онлайн курс «HTML5» / «CSS3»

«Solol earn»

Июль, 2021 — Январь, 2022

Обучающие курсы «Базовые знания программирования и алгоритмов с использованием языков С и JS»

«IT Class» / Гомель

2006 - 2008

Обучение профессии «Оператор ЭВМ»

УО «Межшкольный УПК №1»

ОПЫТ РАБОТЫ

2018 — 2022

Главный инженер

ООО «Промподготовка» / Гомель

2015 — 2018

Преподаватель

ЧУО «Центр подготовки, повышения квалификации и переподготовки рабочих «Промподготовка-Образование» / Гомель

2013 — 2015

Инженер-технолог

ОАО «Гомельский литейных завод «ЦЕНТРОЛИТ» / Гомель

РЕКОМЕНДАЦИИ

А.Н. Черненков

Email: dkranprom@mail.ru

C.A. IIIeruor

ЧУО «Промподготовка-Образование» / Директор

Email: prompodgotovka@mail.ru